<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Digital Site using Hugo &amp; Github Pages</title>
    <link>http://digital.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My Digital Site using Hugo &amp; Github Pages</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 13:09:42 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://digital.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Using a Weber Kettle to Cook a Great Smoked Brisket!</title>
      <link>http://digital.github.io/post/smokedbrisket/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 13:09:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://digital.github.io/post/smokedbrisket/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Want to cook a great smoked brisket but don&amp;rsquo;t want to invest in an expensive smoker or the 8 to 12 hours it takes to cook a brisket in a smoker? This article describes how to cook a great smoked brisket in 3 and 1/2 hours using a Weber Kettle and your oven.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Set Up a Raspberry Pi Cluster</title>
      <link>http://digital.github.io/post/how_to_set_up_a_raspberry_pi_cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 13:01:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://digital.github.io/post/how_to_set_up_a_raspberry_pi_cluster/</guid>
      <description>Photo by Jonathan on Unsplash
 The full text of this article can be found on Medium.  This article covers what you need to know to setup your own Raspberry Pi cluster, including you what you need to buy, how to install the OS and configure the Raspberry Pis, how to set up networking, and other things you need to know to sinplify ongoing administration and maintenance of the cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Develop and Deploy Kubernetes Applications on a Raspberry Pi Cluster</title>
      <link>http://digital.github.io/post/develop_and_deploy_kubernetes_applications_on_a_raspberry_pi_cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 01:01:31 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://digital.github.io/post/develop_and_deploy_kubernetes_applications_on_a_raspberry_pi_cluster/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Want to set up a Kubernetes lab, but don&amp;rsquo;t want use Minikube or spend a lot of money on hardware. This is the first post in a series that describes how to set up a complete Kubernetes cluster on a cluster of Raspberry Pis. This will include topics such as setting up a logging infrastructure, monitoring, Ingress, and other platform level capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
